<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Academic</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Academic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Group One</title>
      <link>/project/group-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/group-one/</guid>
      <description>Logic of social structure and social influence We emphasize the importance of social relations, and will study systematically how they play a role in social communication. We will explore social phenomena using tools from logic and computer science, specifically the mechanisms by which these phenomena can emerge from discrete interactions between individuals. As an example, the diffusion of an idea within a community can be modelled using cellular automata or dynamic modal logic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Two</title>
      <link>/project/group-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/group-two/</guid>
      <description>Belief revision guided by evidence and trust Agents change their belief and opinions in social networks, under the influence of other agents. Rational agents do so with a reason, they may collect evidence, or argument, to justify what they do. There are various frameworks that have been developed to model it. For this project, we would like to compare the existing frameworks, and develop some tools that can help us to see how the opinions with evidence would spread and so that we could make predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Three</title>
      <link>/project/group-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/group-three/</guid>
      <description>Modeling formation and dynamics of social norms This has a close relationship with the theory of values/preference. In particular, we ask the following questions: how to aggregate / relate individual values, responsibilities, actions to collective/social values, responsibilities, actions? again, does social structures influence the process of aggregation? if so, how? Next, regarding the formation of social norms which has been studied by computer science through simulations, can we say anything about it from a logical point of view?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Four</title>
      <link>/project/group-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/group-four/</guid>
      <description>Strategical reasoning in social networks Games are a powerful method for analyzing social practices, but also for designing new practices. They are also attractive because of their perspicuous links with logic and computation. In this part, we will study a variety of graph games that model various basic social scenarios, and we do so in tandem with the development of new dynamic logics that specify properties of the games and that encode reasoning about players, equilibira and long-term temporal evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>